<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<article>
    <preamble>Torres.pdf</preamble>
    <titre>Summary Evaluation with and without References</titre>
    <auteurs>
        <auteur>
            <name>Impossible de trouver l'auteur correspondant à cet email.</name>
            <mail>juan-manuel.torres@univ-avignon.fr</mail>
            <affiliation>juan-manuel.torres@univ-avignon.fr;eric.sanjuan@univ-avignon.fr;horacio.saggion@upf.edu;iria.dacunha@upf.edu;velazquez@yahoo.com</affiliation>
        </auteur>
        <auteur>
            <name>Impossible de trouver l'auteur correspondant à cet email.</name>
            <mail>eric.sanjuan@univ-avignon.fr</mail>
            <affiliation>juan-manuel.torres@univ-avignon.fr;eric.sanjuan@univ-avignon.fr;horacio.saggion@upf.edu;iria.dacunha@upf.edu;velazquez@yahoo.com</affiliation>
        </auteur>
        <auteur>
            <name>Impossible de trouver l'auteur correspondant à cet email.</name>
            <mail>horacio.saggion@upf.edu</mail>
            <affiliation>juan-manuel.torres@univ-avignon.fr;eric.sanjuan@univ-avignon.fr;horacio.saggion@upf.edu;iria.dacunha@upf.edu;velazquez@yahoo.com</affiliation>
        </auteur>
        <auteur>
            <name>Impossible de trouver l'auteur correspondant à cet email.</name>
            <mail>iria.dacunha@upf.edu</mail>
            <affiliation>juan-manuel.torres@univ-avignon.fr;eric.sanjuan@univ-avignon.fr;horacio.saggion@upf.edu;iria.dacunha@upf.edu;velazquez@yahoo.com</affiliation>
        </auteur>
        <auteur>
            <name>Impossible de trouver l'auteur correspondant à cet email.</name>
            <mail>velazquez@yahoo.com</mail>
            <affiliation>juan-manuel.torres@univ-avignon.fr;eric.sanjuan@univ-avignon.fr;horacio.saggion@upf.edu;iria.dacunha@upf.edu;velazquez@yahoo.com</affiliation>
        </auteur>
    </auteurs>
    <abstract>Abstract—Weevaluationa new content-based method forsystems withoutthehuman models which is used to produce system rankings.The research is carried out using a new content-basedevaluation framework called FRESA to compute a variety ofdivergences among probability distributions. We apply ourcomparison framework to various well-established content-basedevaluation measures in text summarization such as COVERAGE,theirRESPONSIVENESS, PYRAMIDSassociationsincludingtextgeneric multi-document summarization in English and French,summarization in English andfocus-based multi-documentgeneric single-document summarization in French and Spanish.summarization tasksand ROUGEin variousstudyingIndex Terms—Text summarization evaluation, content-basedevaluation measures, divergences.</abstract>
    <biblio>[1] I. Mani, G. Klein, D. House, L. Hirschman, T. Firmin, andB. Sundheim, “Summac: a text summarization evaluation,” NaturalLanguage Engineering, vol. 8, no. 1, pp. 43–68, 2002.[2] P. Over, H. Dang, and D. Harman, “DUC in context,” IPM, vol. 43,no. 6, pp. 1506–1520, 2007.[3] Proceedings of the Text Analysis Conference. Gaithesburg, Maryland,USA: NIST, November 17-19 2008.[4] K. Sp¨arck Jones and J. Galliers, Evaluating Natural LanguageProcessing Systems, An Analysis and Review, ser. Lecture Notes inComputer Science. Springer, 1996, vol. 1083.[5] R. L. Donaway, K. W. Drummey, and L. A. Mather, “A comparison ofrankings produced by summarization evaluation measures,” in NAACLWorkshop on Automatic Summarization, 2000, pp. 69–78.[6] H. Saggion, D. Radev, S. Teufel, and W. Lam, “Meta-evaluationof Summaries in a Cross-lingual Environment using Content-basedMetrics,” in COLING 2002, Taipei, Taiwan, August 2002, pp. 849–855.[7] D. R. Radev, S. Teufel, H. Saggion, W. Lam, J. Blitzer, H. Qi, A. C¸ elebi,D. Liu, and E. Dr´abek, “Evaluation challenges in large-scale documentsummarization,” in ACL’03, 2003, pp. 375–382.[8] K. Papineni, S. Roukos, T. Ward, , and W. J. Zhu, “BLEU: a methodfor automatic evaluation of machine translation,” in ACL’02, 2002, pp.311–318.[9] K. Pastra and H. Saggion, “Colouring summaries BLEU,” in EvaluationInitiatives in Natural Language Processing. Budapest, Hungary: EACL,14 April 2003.[10] C.-Y. Lin, “ROUGE: A Package for Automatic Evaluation ofSummaries,” in Text Summarization Branches Out: ACL-04 Workshop,M.-F. Moens and S. Szpakowicz, Eds., Barcelona, July 2004, pp. 74–81.[11] A. Nenkova and R. J. Passonneau, “Evaluating Content Selection inSummarization: The Pyramid Method,” in HLT-NAACL, 2004, pp.145–152.[12] A. Louis and A. Nenkova, “Automatically Evaluating Content Selectionin Summarization without Human Models,” in Empirical Methods inNatural Language Processing, Singapore, August 2009, pp. 306–314.[Online]. Available: http://www.aclweb.org/anthology/D/D09/D09-1032[13] J. Lin, “Divergence Measures based on the Shannon Entropy,” IEEETransactions on Information Theory, vol. 37, no. 145-151, 1991.[14] C.-Y. Lin and E. Hovy, “Automatic Evaluation of Summaries UsingN-gram Co-occurrence Statistics,” in HLT-NAACL. Morristown, NJ,USA: Association for Computational Linguistics, 2003, pp. 71–78.[15] C.-Y. Lin, G. Cao, J. Gao, and J.-Y. Nie, “An information-theoreticapproach to automatic evaluation of summaries,” in HLT-NAACL,Morristown, USA, 2006, pp. 463–470.[16] S. Kullback and R. Leibler, “On information and sufﬁciency,” Ann. ofMath. Stat., vol. 22, no. 1, pp. 79–86, 1951.[17] S. Siegel and N. Castellan, Nonparametric Statistics for the BehavioralSciences. McGraw-Hill, 1998.Summary Evaluation with and without References19Polibits (42) 2010&#12;</biblio>
</article>
